<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pheelosophy on Wierd Reveries</title>
    <link>https://lolwierd.ml/tags/pheelosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pheelosophy on Wierd Reveries</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://lolwierd.ml/tags/pheelosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Two ways to live</title>
      <link>https://lolwierd.ml/posts/2-ways/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolwierd.ml/posts/2-ways/</guid>
      <description>As far as I understand, there are 2 ways to live.
With ambition and without ambition. With dreams, like every other shonen protagonist and like Denji.
I am halfway through Chainsaw Man, and it has moved me to an extent where I am forced to rethink how I view my life as a whole.
This is not a post analyzing or breaking apart Chainsaw Man. I would hate that.
This is rather an exploration of how I am living my life right now, and how this beautiful piece of literature forced me to rethink that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One of the Most Important Posts I will write</title>
      <link>https://lolwierd.ml/posts/one-of-the-most-important-posts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 23:36:21 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lolwierd.ml/posts/one-of-the-most-important-posts/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t feel the need to win. Don&amp;rsquo;t feel the need to be perfect.
Whenever you feel stuck, or overwhelmed, go back to the basics.
 If you have a sense of entitlement to the result, then lack of it will beat your spirits and you&amp;rsquo;ll obsess more over it than your work And even worse trap is doing nothing because results aren&amp;rsquo;t guaranteed. ~Nikhil
  The thing is Results are never guaranteed There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of things that aren&amp;rsquo;t under my control And these factors will limit how much I can achieve, how much I can get Instead being sad about it I should focus on doing my work because then only, I will be able to do the best I can possibly do.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
